# Farzan **Devlaliwalla**Electrical And Electronic Engineering Student

**Address** Perth, WA 6155 **Phone** 0413458042

E-mail farzan.d03@gmail.com

High-energy student undertaking a Bachelor of Electrical and Electronic Engineering degree at Curtin University. Committed to contribute to organizational success while developing new skills and gaining real-world experience. Highly responsible with strong communication and critical thinking skills, and extensive experience in team settings and leadership positions.

# **Work History**

## 2023-03 - EdConnect Mentor Volunteer

#### Current

EdConnect, Perth, WA

- Built valuable relationships with children from low socio-economic backgrounds whilst providing support and mentorship.
- Monitored classrooms for safety and good behavior, offering students positive reinforcement to maintain discipline.
- Worked with over 5 different classroom teachers to learn about current educational standards and best practices for working with children.

#### 2022-11 - 2023-

### **BHP First Year Intern**

01

BHP, Perth, WA

- Cultivated interpersonal skills by building positive relationships with others through networking and group projects.
- Maintained clear and succinct records, reflections and summaries of daily learnings.
- Conducted research to identify an issue within the company and present a solution.

#### 2022-07 -

## **STEM Study Buddy Volunteer**

Current

Curtin University, Bentley, WA

- Developed enrichment materials resource files for use in tutorial sessions.
- Assisted classes of over 20 students using curriculum and materials provided by program.

#### 2021-11 -

#### **Front End Cashier**

Current

Woolworths, Harrisdale, WA

- Determined customer requirements and suggested ideal product offerings to meet needs and boost revenue.
- Monitored self-checkout systems and provided help in resolving complex problems.

#### 2022-05 - 2023-02

**Student Tutor** 

Carey Baptist College Harrisdale, Harrisdale, WA

- Applied different teaching techniques to improve student grades, build test skills and foster classroom confidence.
- Planned individual weekly 1 hour lessons to strengthen weak subjects and build skills for over 4 students.

#### 2021-12 - 2022- Community Volunteer

Save The Children, Southern River, WA

• Effectively worked with team to increase amount of care packages sent out from 40 per week to 50 per week.

 Attained and tracked 50 hours of personal volunteering experience in spreadsheets for mandatory reporting.

#### 2019-07 - 2021- Kitchen Hand

07

07

KFC, Harrisdale, WA

- Inspected equipment, refrigerators and high temperature cookers to check compliance with safe operating levels.
- Followed proper handling and sanitation procedures to comply with food safety standards and protocols.

## Education

#### 2022-02 - Bachelor of Electrical And Electronic Engineering

Current

11

Curtin University - Bentley, WA

Studying with a current course weighted average of 84%

2016-02 - 2021-

**High School Graduate** 

Carey Baptist College - Harrisdale, WA

Graduated Carey Baptist College as Proxime Accessit, with an ATAR of 98.1

## **Accomplishments**

- · 2022 Semester 2 Member of the Vice-Chancellors List (top 1% of cohort).
- · Recipient of 2022 Dean Letter of Commendation for Semester 1 and 2.
- · Recipient of Curtin Extra Tier 1 Certificate for volunteering.
- · Recipient of 2022 Curtin University Academic Excellence Scholarship.
- · Recipient of February 2022, Save the Childrens volunteer of the month award.
- · Recipient of Carey Baptist Medal of Academic Excellence from 2016-2022.
- · Recipient of 2021 Carey Baptist Proxime Accessit award.
- Leader of 2020 Carey Baptist College STEM Solar Car Challenge state team.
- · Represented Carey Baptist College in the 2019 CO2 dragster state competition.
- · Represented Carey Baptist College in multiple interstate swimming competitions.

## **Skills and Interests**

Multilingual: fluent in Hindi, Gujarati, English

Great teamwork and leadership skills

High level of emotional intelligence

Avid swimmer, tennis player and martial artist

Movie and novel enthusiast